<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LangChain Journey - Model</title>
      <link>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/langchain_model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/langchain_model/</guid>
      <description>01 What is LangChain? LangChain is a framework for LLM application development (resource: langchain). That is to say, if you want to learn the framework to train LLM, refer to PyTorch. If you want to learn the framework to build LLM applications, refer to LangChain.
You can simple refer to the conceptual guide and high level from langchain officials as well.
02 Core Components of LangChain The core components of LangChain library include</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch Journey - Background</title>
      <link>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/pytorch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/pytorch/</guid>
      <description>01 Introduction For some people, understanding the development history of a technology may not be important. However, personally, I find it difficult to absorb knowledge without knowing at least part of its background. If you&amp;rsquo;re the type of person who prefers to skip the history and jump straight into practical applications, feel free to skip this page and dive directly into the technical content.
02 History In this section, I will introduce the history of PyTorch through its version updates, which I believe is the best way to illustrate its evolution and improvements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website Using Hugo &amp; GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/hugo_github/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/hugo_github/</guid>
      <description>01 Why Hugo &amp;amp; GitHub Pages? I chose Hugo because its templates are more visually appealing compared to Jekyll&amp;rsquo;s. GitHub Pages is an excellent hosting option for static websites since it is free and easy to use.
02 Pre-Build Preparation Before using a Hugo template, I recommend watching this playlist:
Hugo - Static Site Generator | Tutorial
Although the playlist is somewhat outdated, most of the steps are still relevant, especially for getting a general understanding of the Hugo framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syntax Page</title>
      <link>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/markdown_syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://poyasharonlin.github.io/website/blog/markdown_syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
